okay let's get ready to meditate okay
[Music]
turn off cell phone
uh we'll do five minutes
on
uh
think about the things you have you own
and how they came from Joe
Joe sent them to you he was dying or she
was dying and she sent this Karma into
the future
the place where you live the things that
you own the friends that you have the
family you're born into
they were all sent by
Joe
DNS
[Music]
o
today
in Como commercials
and it's because Joe was very generous
Joe enjoyed giving to other people
sharing
and every day you have
your city your friends your clothes your
Electronics you're using up those seats
you are using up that debit card
okay here we go
just try very hard to focus for five
minutes
concentration
come back here Brad come back to your
bed
then slowly open your eyes
foreign